(Howard:)But how's this all gonna work?
(Howard:)Do we get a nanny?
(Howard:)I mean, can we
afford a nanny?
(Howard:)And if we can,
we can't get a pretty one,
(Howard:)'cause it'll wreck our marriage.
(Howard:)We can't get an ugly one,
'cause it'll scare the kid.
I-I don't know, Howie.
(Howard:)Are we in a good
school district?
(Howard:)You're Catholic, I'm Jewish.
(Howard:)What religion do
we raise it?
(Howard:)And if it's a boy,
do we get him circumcised?
(Howard:)People say it's barbaric,
(Howard:)but if we don't, it looks like
a pig in a blanket.
(Bernadette:)Calm down, it's
gonna be okay.
(Howard:)How's it gonna be okay?
(Howard:)Look at me, I'm a mess.
(Howard:)And that means this baby's
gonna half a mess.
(Howard:)And that's even
before we screw it up
(Howard:)with our cut-rate
moderately attractive nanny.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪